<msdyn_plan msdyn_planid="71a5c7e0-0aa3-f011-bbd2-6045bde61f12">
  <iscustomizable>1</iscustomizable>
  <msdyn_content mimetype="application/octet-stream">content</msdyn_content>
  <msdyn_contentschemaversion>1.1</msdyn_contentschemaversion>
  <msdyn_description>This solution enables SPL Services to manage procurement, product catalogs, approvals, and PO lifecycle efficiently with data-driven insights.</msdyn_description>
  <msdyn_languagecode>1033</msdyn_languagecode>
  <msdyn_name>Centralized PO Management Hub</msdyn_name>
  <msdyn_prompt>Our organization (SPL Services) needs a centralized Purchase Order Management System to manage product catalogs, procurement requests, approvals, and tracking — all built on Microsoft Power Apps and Dataverse.

The solution should:
1. Centralize Item &amp; Product Data
Use a main table called PO Item Database with attributes like ItemCode, ItemName, RFID, WeightPurchaseUnit, WeightSalesUnit, Remarks, and ForeignName.
Connect to lookup tables for Pool Group, Catalog Group, Colour, Pattern, Material, and Size.
Allow linking items to multiple Colour, Material, Pattern, and Size entries through intermediate (join) tables like ItemColour, ItemMaterial, ItemPattern, and ItemSize.
2. Manage the Procurement Lifecycle
Include tables for Purchase Orders, Purchase Order Lines, Suppliers, Locations, and Status Tracking.
Purchase Orders should move through these stages: Draft → Submitted → Approved → Ordered → Received → Closed.
Line items link to PO Item Database records.
3. Provide Two Integrated Power Apps:
A Canvas App (called SPL – PO Manager) for staff to:
Create new purchase orders
Search and filter products by Pool, Catalog, or RFID
Add multiple items to a PO
Submit for approval and track status
A Model-Driven App (called SPL – Procurement Inventory Manager) for procurement staff to:
Maintain the product catalog and lookup data
Approve submitted purchase orders
Manage suppliers, update item details, and track deliveries.
4. Automate Approvals &amp; Notifications
Create a Power Automate flow that triggers when a Purchase Order is submitted.
Sends approval requests to the Finance Approver group.
On approval, updates the PO status and sends notifications to the requester.
Logs actions (who approved, when, and comments) in an Audit Log table.
5. Role-Based Permissions
Purchaser: Can create and view their own POs.
Procurement Manager: Can edit all items, approve requests, and manage catalogs.
Finance Approver: Can review and approve submitted POs only.
6. Scalability &amp; Reporting
Built on Dataverse for future integration with Power BI and SharePoint.
Include a sample dashboard showing POs by status, spend by supplier, and average approval time.
Please use the above structure as the foundation.
Generate a complete Copilot plan with a clear business problem, purpose, user roles, data model, apps, and flows, ready for extension using the existing Dataverse tables in the SPL-PO-Manager solution.</msdyn_prompt>
  <statecode>0</statecode>
  <statuscode>1</statuscode>
</msdyn_plan>